♪
- Aw, look at you kids.
哎呀，看看你们这些孩子。
I can't believe you've been the face
我真不敢相信你已经成为了诚实亚伯轮胎的代言人12年了。
of Honest Abe's Tires for 12 years.
哦，你们长得真快。
Oh, you're growing up so fast.
她知道那些胡子是假的，对吧？
- She knows the beards are fake, right?
我只是喜欢我们拍这个广告的时候。
- I just love when we shoot this commercial.
我们也是。
all: Us too.
我讨厌我们拍这个广告的时候。
- I hate it when we shoot this commercial.
我的胡子很痒。
- My beard is itchy. - I'm a girl. I don't even get
我是女孩。我甚至不明白为什么我会有胡子。
why I have a beard.
为什么我会有胡子。
- I don't get why we keep doing
我不明白我们为什么一直拍
this dumb commercial.
这个愚蠢的广告。
- Because Mom loves it, and Dad gets free tires.
因为妈妈喜欢，爸爸还能免费得到轮胎。
- But what's the connection between us and tires?
但我们和轮胎有什么联系呢？
- It's because...
这是因为...
"We're the Harper Quadruplets.
"我们是哈珀四胞胎。
"And like the four of us,
"就像我们四个一样，
the tires of a car are the same age..."
汽车的轮胎也是同一年代的..."
all: "And work in perfect harmony."
大家齐声说："并且完美和谐地工作。"
- It's the same lame script every year.
每年都是这个老套的剧本。
- Have you guys seen this year's script? It's genius!
你们看过今年的剧本了吗？太天才了！
You've done it again, Honest Abe.
你又做到了，诚实的亚伯。
- These quads are the best thing that have ever happened
这四胞胎是我轮胎生意发生过的最好的事情。
to my tire business. - Aww.
哇。
- I feel like we've become family.
我感觉我们已经成为一家人了。
Nice to see you again, Girl Quad,
很高兴再次见到你，女孩四胞胎，
Short Quad, Cute Quad, and You Quad.
矮个四胞胎，可爱四胞胎，还有你四胞胎。
- Well, Mom and Dad Quad are gonna browse the tires.
嗯，爸爸妈妈四胞胎要去看看轮胎。
- Anything you want, and grab yourself
想要什么就随便拿，再给自己拿一个
an Honest Abe air freshener.
一个诚实的亚伯车载香氛。
Here, kids.
来，孩子们。
You can have some too.
你们也可以拿一些。
The scent is in the beard.
香味在胡子里。
- Ah, I got ocean breeze.
- 啊，我拿到海洋微风。
- Ah, I got icy mint.
- 啊，我拿到冰凉薄荷。
- I got autumn leaves.
- 我拿到秋叶。
- I got middle-aged beard.
- 我拿到中年胡须。
- It's good to be a quad, isn't it?
- 成为四胞胎真好，不是吗？
- Is it?
- 是吗？
Is this what being a quad has come to?
这就是当四轮车手的下场吗？
Sniffing beards and being called "Girl Quad"?
闻胡子还被叫做'女四轮车手'？
- It's better than "Short Quad."
- 总比'矮四轮车手'好。
- I'm just "You Quad."
- 我就只是'你四轮车手'。
- "Cute Quad" isn't so bad,
- '可爱四轮车手'还不算太糟，
but I'm offended for you guys.
但我觉得你们被冒犯了。
- The point is, he doesn't even know our names.
- 关键是，他甚至不知道我们的名字。
He's just using us because we're quads.
他只是利用我们因为我们都是四轮车手。
- Yeah, like we're some sort of freak show.
- 对啊，好像我们是某种怪胎秀一样。
Uh, Dawn, your lady beard's crooked.
呃，Dawn，你的女士胡子歪了。
- Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
Wait, what am I doing?
等等，我在做什么？
Look, I am sick of doing this same commercial
看，我厌倦了每年都做这个同样的广告。
every year.
每年都这样。
- Yeah. - Me too.
是啊。
- I'm over it.
我也是。
- What's the matter, quads?
我受够了。
- You know, we're not just quads.
怎么了，四胞胎？
We have names.
你知道，我们不仅仅是四胞胎。
I'm Dawn. That's Nicky.
我们有名字。我是Dawn。那是Nicky。
That's Ricky; that's-- - I'm good with Cute Quad.
那是Ricky；那是-- - 我觉得Cute Quad挺好的。
- Admit it. You're only using us
- 承认吧。你只是因为我们
because we're quads.
是四胞胎才利用我们。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
Of course I am.
当然是的。
- We're not even getting anything out of it.
- 我们甚至从中得不到任何东西。
I mean, our dad gets tires,
我是说，我们的爸爸得到了轮胎，
but what about us?
但我们呢？
- Yeah, it's not like we get to get cool outfits
- 是啊，我们又不能得到酷炫的服装
or go on tour as spokespeople.
或者作为代言人去巡回演出。
- Yeah, or get a limo
是的，或者坐豪华轿车
with an ice-cream sundae bar.
里面还有冰淇淋圣代吧。
- Well, that's just crazy talk.
嗯，那只是疯狂的想法。
Is this about the air fresheners?
这是关于空气清新剂的事吗？
You Quad, swap with Girl Quad.
你们四胞胎，和女孩四胞胎换一下。
- This is not about the air fresheners.
这不是关于空气清新剂的事。
This is about being more than just quads.
这是关于不仅仅是四胞胎的事。
- But you're the most famous quads
但你们是博尔德最有名的四胞胎
in all of Boulder
还有丹佛的一半。
and half of Denver.
不再是了。
- Not anymore.
Our days as the Harper Quads...
我们作为Harper四胞胎的日子...
are over.
结束了。
- What are you saying?
你在说什么？
- We're re-tire-ing.
我们要退休了。
Up top.
在上面。
- Wait a minute. You're quitting?
等等，你们要退出？
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Who's quitting?
哇，哇，哇，哇。谁要退出？
all: We are.
我们。
- What?
什么？
- We don't want to be in this commercial anymore.
- 我们不想再参与这个广告了。
- Fine.
- 好吧。
No commercial,
没有广告，
no beards,
没有胡须，
no air fresheners, nothing!
没有空气清新剂，什么都没有！
- What--what about our new tires?
- 那我们的新轮胎呢？
- No tires! - Aww.
- 没有轮胎！ - 哎呀。
- Well, Tom, if the kids don't want to do it,
- 嗯，汤姆，如果孩子们不想做，
they don't have to do it.
他们就不必做。
- Honey, he already took
- 亲爱的，他已经把
last year's tires off our car.
去年我们车上的轮胎已经拆下来了。
- Parenting, Tom.
- 育儿，汤姆。
Hey, I am proud of you for standing up for yourselves.
嘿，我为你们能为自己挺身而出感到骄傲。
all: Thanks, Mom.
大家：谢谢妈妈。
- We have no tires!
- 我们没有轮胎了！
- Thomas Louise Harper!
- 托马斯·路易斯·哈珀！
- It is Louis.
- 是路易。
The hospital spelled it wrong.
医院拼错了。
- And we're not leaving here with nothing.
- 我们不会空手离开这里。
The Harper family...
哈珀家族...
is walking out of here with our dignity.
我们带着尊严离开这里。
- Right.
- 对。
Run, Anne!
跑，安妮！
[crashing]
[碰撞声]
- Well, there goes the dignity.
- 好吧，尊严没了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ One, two ♪ ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪
- So you guys just quit your big tire commercial?
所以你们就放弃了那个大轮胎广告？
- We didn't quit.
我们没有放弃。
We re-tire-d.
我们重新轮胎了。
Up top.
向上。
- But you guys were, like,
但你们曾经是，比如，
the most famous quads in Boulder.
你们可是博尔德最有名的四头肌。
- And half of Denver.
- 还有丹佛的一半。
- Attention, students.
- 同学们注意了。
I have two announcements.
我有两则通知。
Apparently, some prankster
显然，有个恶作剧者
thought it would be funny
觉得在我的鞋子里放博洛尼亚香肠会很有趣。
to put bologna in my shoes.
好吧，笑话在他们身上。
Well, the joke's on them.
这不仅给了我很好的足弓支撑，
Not only does it give me a nice arch support,
而且我的乌龟雪莉还能享用到
but my turtle Shelly gets the treat
美味的脚肉。
of some sweet feet meat.
给龟龟谢莉来点甜甜脚肉。
Carry on. Let's go, Shelly.
继续前进。走吧，谢莉。
- Um, weren't there two announcements, Principal Tarian?
呃，不是有两个公告吗，塔里安校长？
- Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Not so fast, Shelly.
别太快，谢莉。
We have some special visitors:
我们有几位特别的访客：
the new faces of Honest Abe's Tires.
诚实亚伯轮胎的新面孔。
- New faces? - He replaced us?
新面孔？他替换了我们？
- And here to introduce the stars
并且来介绍诚实亚伯四重唱巡演的明星...
of Honest Abe's Four-Part Harmony Tour...
他就是诚实亚伯本人。
- He's taking them on tour?
- 他带他们去巡演？
- Is Honest Abe himself.
- 就是诚实亚伯本人。
- Thank you.
- 谢谢。
Let's give a warm welcome
让我们热烈欢迎
to the adorable Kramden Quads:
可爱的克拉姆登四胞胎：
Emma, Jules, George, and Lyle.
艾玛、朱尔斯、乔治和莱尔。
[applause]
[掌声]
- He knows their names?
- 他知道他们的名字？
- What makes them so special?
- 他们有什么特别之处？
- Well, you don't see quadruplets every day.
- 嗯，你不是每天都能见到四胞胎的。
- Uh, hello?
呃，你好？
We're quadruplets.
我们是四胞胎。
- Yeah, but not the matching kind.
是的，但不是那种一模一样的。
- We could dress up like that if we wanted to,
如果我们愿意，我们可以那样打扮，
but we're not some cheap novelty act.
但我们不是什么廉价的噱头表演。
- Hit it, quads!
开始吧，四胞胎！
all: ♪ Come in and learn the power of four ♪
♪ 进来学习 ♪
♪ At Honest Abe's Tire Store ♪
♪ 四倍的力量 ♪
♪ Take it from ♪ - ♪ Me ♪ - ♪ Me ♪
♪ 在诚实亚伯轮胎店 ♪
- ♪ Me ♪ - ♪ Me ♪
♪ 从我这里 ♪ ♪ 我这里 ♪ ♪ 我这里 ♪ ♪ 我这里 ♪
all: ♪ The tires work ♪
大家：♪ 轮胎运转 ♪
♪ In four-part harmony ♪
♪ 以四重和谐 ♪
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Wow. That was pretty amazing.
- 哇。那真是相当惊人。
- I know, right?
- 我知道，对吧？
- Well, we could sing like that if we wanted to.
- 嗯，如果我们想的话，我们也可以那样唱歌。
- Really? Since when?
- 真的吗？从什么时候开始？
- Since now. Hit it, boys!
- 从现在开始。来吧，男孩们！
[all singing off-key] ♪ Take it from me ♪ - ♪ Me ♪
[大家唱得走调] ♪ 从我这里学 ♪ - ♪ 我 ♪
- ♪ Me ♪ - ♪ Me ♪
- ♪ 我 ♪ - ♪ 我 ♪
[all singing off-key]
♪ The tires work ♪
♪ 轮胎工作 ♪
♪ In four-part harmony ♪
♪ 四重和谐 ♪
[grating tune]
- You four, hush.
- 你们四个，安静。
The quads are singing.
四胞胎在唱歌。
- Hit it, quads!
- 开始吧，四胞胎！
all: ♪ Come in and learn ♪
所有人: ♪ 进来学习 ♪
♪ The power of four ♪
♪ 四重力量 ♪
♪ Of Honest Abe's Tire Store ♪
♪ 亚伯轮胎店的 ♪
[upbeat music]
[metallic scraping]
- Is that your father?
- 那是你父亲吗？
- Yeah, he's sparking.
- 是的，他在打火。
- Don't you mean parking?
- 你不是想说停车吗？
- Nope.
- 不是。
- You know, I would've thought your dad would have
- 你知道吗，我本以为你爸爸现在会
bought new tires by now.
买新轮胎了。
- Yeah, we all would've thought.
- 是啊，我们都这么以为。
[metallic scraping]
- Or at least switched his carpool day.
或者至少换一天拼车。
- So how was school?
学校怎么样？
- It was weird for...
对我们来说都有点怪...
[all singing off-key] ♪ Me ♪
♪ 我 ♪
- It was weird for all of us.
我们大家都有点不适应。
- Honest Abe replaced us with new quads
老实说，亚伯把我们换成了新的四人组，
and brought them to school to talk about tire safety.
还带他们去学校讲轮胎安全。
- Oh, and the principal showed off his sweet feet meat.
哦，校长还炫耀了他的美脚。
[metallic scraping]
♪ 钢铁刮擦声 ♪
- Ugh. So are you guys
你们对此感到不高兴吗？
upset about this?
对这件事感到不高兴吗？
- No. - Not at all.
- 不。 - 一点也不。
- Don't be ridiculous. - I'm good.
- 别开玩笑了。 - 我很好。
[metallic scraping]
[金属刮擦声]
- This is so much better!
- 这好多了！
[all yelp]
[所有人惊叫]
- Hi. - Sorry to bother you,
- 嗨。 - 抱歉打扰你们，
but didn't you guys used to be the Harper Quads?
但你们以前不是哈珀家的四胞胎吗？
- "Used to be"?
- “以前是”？
- We just wanted you to know
- 我们只是想让你们知道
that you were our greatest inspiration.
你们曾经是我们最大的灵感来源。
- Wait, "were"?
等等，‘曾经’？
- Yeah, you know, before you re-tire-d.
是啊，你知道的，在你们‘退休’之前。
[all laughing]
[所有人笑]
- Oh, I get it now.
哦，我现在明白了。
"Re-tire-d."
‘退休’。
Why didn't you say it funny like them?
你们为什么不学他们那样幽默地说呢？
- We're just so grateful that you guys
我们只是非常感激你们
gave us the opportunity
给了我们这个机会
to become the most famous quads in all of Boulder.
成为博尔德最著名的四胞胎。
- And half of Denver.
还有丹佛的一半。
- Abe thinks we can go full Denver.
亚伯认为我们可以征服整个丹佛。
- Ah, youth.
啊，青春。
- It goes downhill pretty fast.
下滑得相当快。
Before you know it, you'll be four nameless lumps
在你意识到之前，你们就会变成四个无名小卒，
with itchy beards.
满脸胡须痒痒的。
- Jules, Emma, Lyle, George,
朱尔斯，艾玛，莱尔，乔治，
there's sundaes waiting for you in the limo.
豪华轿车里有圣代冰淇淋等着你们。
- Got to go!
得走了！
- Thanks again!
再次感谢！
- That should be our limo.
那是我们的豪华轿车。
- Yeah, and our ice cream.
对，还有我们的冰淇淋。
- We've got to get our commercial back.
我们得拿回我们的广告。
- At least we've got bologna in our shoes.
至少我们鞋子里还有博洛尼亚香肠。
What? I'm the only one?
什么？只有我一个人吗？
- This is why we never went full Denver.
这就是我们从未完全去丹佛的原因。
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Honk, honk. Quad-mobile comin' through.
按喇叭，四轮车来了。
- We just drove over to humbly ask for our jobs back.
我们只是开车过来谦卑地请求恢复我们的工作。
- What?
- 什么？
- Oh, let us roll down the window.
- 哦，让我们把窗户摇下来。
[grunting]
[咕哝声]
We want our jobs back.
我们要回我们的工作。
- Look, can I be frank with you?
- 听着，我能坦白说吗？
- Hey, man, it's 2016.
- 嘿，伙计，这是2016年。
You be who you got to be.
你做你该做的。
- When you guys were kids,
- 当你们还是孩子的时候，
your quad light shone bright,
你们的四轮光芒闪耀，
but the other day, I saw that light go out.
但前几天，我看到那光芒熄灭了。
- No, we've still got our quad light.
- 不，我们还有我们的四重光。
Hit it, boys. - Hit what?
- 来吧，男孩们。 - 来什么？
- You're not the boss of me. - What's a quad light?
- 你不是我的老板。 - 什么是四重光？
- This is exactly what I'm talking about.
- 这正是我所说的。
The Kramdens never disagree.
克拉门一家从不争吵。
Sorry, kids.
对不起，孩子们。
You had your run, but now you're done.
你们已经风光过了，但现在结束了。
- They never disagree? How is that possible?
- 他们从不争吵？这怎么可能？
- It's not. All brothers and sisters fight.
- 不可能。所有的兄弟姐妹都会吵架。
It's natural. - Yeah, we fight all the time.
这是自然的。 - 是的，我们经常吵架。
- No, we don't. - Yes, we do.
- 不，我们没有。 - 是的，我们有。
- No, we don't. - You're fighting right now.
- 不，我们没有。 - 你现在就在争吵。
- No, we're not. - Yeah, we are.
- 不，我们没有。 - 是的，我们有。
- No, we're not. - Yes, we are!
- 不，我们没有。 - 是的，我们有！
- Just stop.
- 停下吧。
See? All brothers and sisters fight.
看吧？所有的兄弟姐妹都会争吵。
- Except the Kramdens,
- 除了克拉姆登家，
which is why this retired Lincoln is thinkin'
这就是为什么这位退休的林肯觉得
something's stinkin'.
有些事情不对劲。
- Maybe the Kramdens don't fight
- 也许克拉姆登家不吵架
because they're not really brothers and sisters.
因为他们不是真正的兄弟姐妹。
- Of course.
- 当然。
They're just pretending to be related
他们只是在假装有血缘关系
to get cool stuff.
为了得到酷炫的东西。
- We got to prove this to Honest Abe.
- 我们必须向诚实的亚伯证明这一点。
He'll never let those fake quads be the face of his store.
他绝不会让那些假四胞胎成为他店铺的门面。
- And when they're out,
- 等他们出局了，
we'll be in.
我们就能上位。
- All right, let's roll.
- 好吧，我们行动吧。
[all saying "beep"]
[所有人发出“哔”声]
- [whistling]
[吹口哨]
- So how can we prove those Kramdens are frauds
那么我们如何证明那些克拉姆登家是骗子
and get our commercial back?
并拿回我们的广告呢？
- Ooh! - What do you got?
哦！
- We could ride around in their limo
你有什么主意？
and eat their ice cream.
我们可以坐他们的豪华轿车
- And how will that prove anything?
吃他们的冰淇淋。
- Well, it--it won't, but at least we get
那怎么能证明什么呢？
to ride around in a limo and eat ice cream.
嗯，这——这不能证明什么，但至少我们可以坐豪华轿车吃冰淇淋。
- Ooh! - What do you got?
- 哦！
- I like Nicky's plan.
- 有什么好主意吗？
- Okay, from now on, if you "ooh,"
- 我喜欢尼基的计划。
you either have to have a good idea,
- 好吧，从现在起，如果你“哦”，
or have to go to the bathroom.
- 你得有个好主意，或者得去厕所。
- Ooh! Mae, doesn't your Mom work at a crime lab?
- 哦！梅，你妈妈不是在犯罪实验室工作吗？
- Now that's how you "ooh."
- 现在那才是正确的“哦”。
- Yeah, my Mom uses DNA all the time
- 是的，我妈妈经常用DNA
to prove all sorts of stuff.
- 来证明各种事情。
- It sounds like this Dee Ennay lady
- 听起来这位D.N.A女士
is doing all the work.
正在做所有的工作。
Maybe we should just go straight to her
也许我们应该直接去找她
and not waste our time with Mae's Mom.
而不是浪费时间在Mae的妈妈身上。
- No, DNA is contained in every cell in the human body,
不，DNA存在于人体每个细胞中，
and it stores all the body's biological information.
它储存了身体所有的生物信息。
People who are related will have similar DNA.
有亲属关系的人会有相似的DNA。
- Like we do. - Exactly.
就像我们一样。
So if the Kramden Quads aren't related,
正是如此。
their DNA will prove it.
所以如果Kramden四胞胎没有亲属关系，
- And since it's in every cell,
他们的DNA会证明这一点。
all you need to do is get a little piece of them,
你只需要取他们一点样本，
like sweat, hair, or fingernails.
比如汗水、头发或指甲。
Ugh, spit or slobber will work too.
呃，口水或唾液也可以。
- Ooh!
哦！
- Do you have an idea of how to get that?
你有办法拿到吗？
- Nope. It's the other "ooh."
没有。是另一个‘哦’。
♪ ♪
- Now, remember, put their DNA samples
现在，记住，把他们的DNA样本
in these bags.
放进这些袋子里。
- There they are.
它们在那儿。
- Ice cream limo, here we come.
冰淇淋豪华轿车，我们来了。
- Hey, Kramdens.
嘿，克拉姆登一家。
Thanks so much for coming.
非常感谢你们的到来。
- Thanks for having us.
谢谢你们的邀请。
- Congrats on being Abe's new faves.
恭喜你们成为亚伯的新宠。
- To celebrate, we've invited you
为了庆祝，我们邀请你们
to "Try It Before You Buy It Day"
参加今天的‘先试后买日’
here at Tom's Get Sporty.
在汤姆的运动装备店。
- Feel free to try out anything you want in the store.
请随意尝试店里的任何东西。
Grab stuff, touch stuff.
拿东西，摸东西。
- Taste stuff.
- 尝尝东西。
Mae, lick a baseball.
Mae, 舔一下棒球。
Show 'em how it's done.
展示给他们看怎么做。
- No.
- 不。
- We'll be around if you have any questions.
- 如果你有任何问题，我们会在这里。
Now go have fun!
现在去玩得开心吧！
♪ ♪
- Ow! Something tore a piece of my fingernail off.
- 哎哟！有什么东西撕掉了我的一块指甲。
♪ ♪
- I got Lyle's ice cream out of the limo.
- 我从豪华轿车里拿出了Lyle的冰淇淋。
- Nicky, you were supposed to get the spoon.
尼基，你本该拿勺子的。
- Oh, I got the spoon.
哦，我拿了勺子。
This is to celebrate.
这是为了庆祝。
♪ ♪
- Ah, those are two good choices,
啊，这两个选择都不错，
and there's only one way to know for sure.
只有一种方法能确定。
Go ahead.
继续。
You know you want to.
你知道你想这么做。
♪ ♪
Good choice.
好选择。
♪ ♪
- This gum you gave me tastes horrible.
- 你给我的这口香糖味道真难吃。
Where can I get rid of it?
我该去哪儿吐掉它？
- Here. - [spits]
- 这儿。 - [吐出]
- Yes, I got it.
- 是的，我拿到了。
Hey.
嘿。
♪ ♪
- Ow! What are you doing?
- 哎哟！你干嘛呢？
- Uh, fishing for compliments.
- 呃，想听点恭维话。
- Were you going to put my hair
- 你是不是打算把我的头发
in that bag? - What bag?
放在那个袋子里？ - 什么袋子？
- The one that says "DNA Sample."
- 那个写着“DNA样本”的袋子。
- Which stands for...
- 意思是...
"Do Not Assume" this is for a DNA sample.
“不要假设”这是用于DNA样本的。
- Why are you guys collecting our DNA?
- 你们为什么要收集我们的DNA？
- Because we know you're not real quadruplets,
- 因为我们知道你们不是真正的四胞胎，
and we're gonna prove it to get our commercial back.
我们要证明这一点来拿回我们的广告。
- Wow, we really used to look up to you guys,
- 哇，我们曾经真的很尊敬你们，
but you've stooped so low.
但你们已经堕落到这种地步了。
- You're a disgrace to quads everywhere.
- 你们是所有四胞胎的耻辱。
- I bet they're not even real quads.
我敢打赌他们根本就不是真正的四胞胎。
[all gasp]
【众人惊讶】
- We're more real quads than you are.
我们比你们更像是真四胞胎。
- Oh, yeah? Prove it.
哦，是吗？证明来看看。
- Oh, we will.
哦，我们会的。
We'll test your DNA and ours,
我们会检测你们和我们的DNA，
and then we'll see who the fraud quads really are.
然后看看谁才是真正的冒牌四胞胎。
♪ ♪
- [panting]
【喘气声】
Great news, kids. The Kramden Quads
孩子们，好消息，克拉姆登四胞胎退出了诚实亚伯的广告。
dropped out of Honest Abe's commercial.
退出了亚伯拉罕·林肯的广告。
- What? - No time for questions.
- 什么？ - 没时间回答问题。
Honest Abe wants you back! - He does?
亚伯拉罕·林肯想让你们回来！ - 真的吗？
- I said "no time for questions"!
- 我说了“没时间回答问题”！
Daddy needs some new tires,
爸爸需要一些新轮胎，
so we got to get back there pronto.
所以我们得赶紧回去。
- No, but Tom, the kids said they don't want
- 不行，汤姆，孩子们说过他们不想再做了，记得吗？ - 那人说“不许问问题”。
to do it anymore, remember? - The man said "no questions."
走吧！
Let's go!
[所有人同时说话]
[all speaking at once]
- Go, go, go, go, go, go!
快走，快走，快走，快走，快走，快走！
- Why do you think the Kramdens
你觉得克拉蒙德一家为什么
dropped out of the commercial?
退出了广告拍摄？
- They must've known we were onto them,
他们肯定知道我们发现了他们的秘密，
and they probably skipped town.
很可能已经逃离了镇子。
- I knew they were fake quads.
我就知道他们是假四胞胎。
- Yeah, real quads never run scared.
没错，真正的四胞胎从不会害怕逃跑。
- Let's go! [all scream]
快走！
- Let's go! Let's go, let's go!
快走！快走，快走！
- [yells]
（大喊）
♪ ♪
- Honest Abe.
- 诚实的亚伯。
Thank you so much for having us back.
非常感谢再次邀请我们。
We are so excited.
我们非常兴奋。
- Well, you're definitely my second choice,
- 好吧，你绝对是我的第二选择，
but at least you were available,
但至少你是有空的，
and I didn't have to get those costumes cleaned.
我也不必让人清洗那些服装。
- Have you ever considered changing your name
- 你有没有考虑过改名为
to "Slightly Honest Abe"
“稍微诚实的亚伯”
and leaving some of these details out?
并省略一些细节？
- Hmm. Let me try that.
嗯，让我试试。
Here, I didn't get these from the trash.
看，这些不是我从垃圾桶里捡来的。
Better?
好些了吗？
- Yes. Thank you.
是的，谢谢你。
- Ew.
哎呀。
These beards are dirty.
这些胡子真脏。
- Is this a blueberry?
这是蓝莓吗？
- Ew, gross.
哎呀，真恶心。
- So what if you got a little blueberry
就算你的垃圾胡子里面有一点蓝莓，
in your trash beards?
那又怎样？
And so what if we didn't get the limo or the ice cream?
那又怎么样，我们没坐上豪华轿车或者吃上冰淇淋？
We got what we wanted.
我们得到了想要的。
We're the Harper Quads again. - Yeah.
我们又是哈珀四胞胎了。- 是啊。
- You're right. - We're back!
- 你说得对。- 我们回来了！
- So you know what I'm gonna do?
所以你知道我要做什么吗？
I'm gonna celebrate by enjoying this blueberry.
我要庆祝一下，享受这个蓝莓。
[spits] Not a blueberry.
[吐出]不是蓝莓。
- Mae, what are you doing here?
- 梅，你在这里干什么？
- I brought the DNA results,
- 我带来了DNA检测结果，
and it's big.
而且很重要。
- Yeah, we know already.
是的，我们已经知道了。
The Kramdens ran away
克拉姆登一家逃走了
because they're not really quads.
因为他们并不是真正的四胞胎。
- They didn't run away.
他们没有逃跑。
They went full Denver.
他们完全变成了丹佛人。
- Wait, so where are they now?
等等，那他们现在在哪里？
- Denver.
在丹佛。
- But then what about the DNA?
但那DNA结果呢？
- Yeah, are they real quads or not?
是啊，他们是真正的四胞胎吗？
- Oh, they're real quads.
哦，他们是真正的四胞胎。
- So then what's the big news? - Yeah.
那么，大新闻是什么？
- You're not.
你不是。
- [gasps] - [whistling]
[吸气声]
- ♪ La la la la la la, la la la la la ♪
[吹口哨]
- It's true.
♪啦啦啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦♪
One of us is not related to the other three.
这是真的。
- But who?
我们中有一个与另外三个没有血缘关系。
- I don't know.
但会是谁呢？
We didn't put labels on our samples
我不知道。
because we assumed we'd all be related.
我们没有在我们的样本上贴标签，因为我们以为我们都会是相关的。
- But we're not.
但我们不是。
One of us is the odd quad out.
我们四人中有一个是外人。
- I said it was big.
我说过它很大。
- But which one of us isn't one of us?
但我们中谁不是我们中的一员？
- We need to get to the bottom of this.
我们需要弄清楚这一点。
Mom, Dad,
妈妈，爸爸，
How long did you think you could keep it a secret from us?
你们以为能对我们隐瞒多久？
- What are you talking about?
你们在说什么？
- We already know.
我们已经知道了。
Just admit it.
承认吧。
- Fine.
好吧。
I took some apples for later.
我拿了一些苹果留着以后吃。
- No, not that.
不，不是那个。
- Fine. It wasn't a typo.
好吧。那不是打字错误。
My middle name really is Louise.
我的中间名真的是Louise。
- We're talking about the secret
我们在说的是我们中的一个
of one of us not being related to the other three.
与另外三个人没有血缘关系的秘密。
- Not related?
没有血缘关系？
That's ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
- We have the DNA results
我们有DNA结果
that prove we're not real quads.
这证明我们不是真正的四胞胎。
- Well, there must be some mistake.
嗯，一定是哪里搞错了。
- Maybe there was a mix-up at the hospital.
也许医院里搞混了。
There were a lot of babies there.
那里有很多婴儿。
Maybe Dad grabbed the wrong one.
可能是爸爸抱错了。
- No way.
不可能。
I know what my babies look like.
我知道我的孩子们长什么样。
It's like these four apples.
就像这四个苹果。
- That one's a pear.
那个是梨。
- Is it?
是吗？
- Harper Quads to the set!
- 哈珀四胞胎到现场！
- Oh, come on, guys, that's you.
- 哦，拜托，伙计们，那就是你们。
all: Is it?
所有人: 是吗？
♪ ♪
- Uh, Nicky, you're in my spot.
- 呃，尼基，你占了我的位置。
- No, this is my spot.
- 不，这是我的位置。
- Nicky's probably the odd quad.
- 尼基可能是那个与众不同的四胞胎。
He does look different from the rest of us.
他看起来确实和我们其他人不一样。
And he loves pasta.
而且他非常喜欢意大利面。
I wonder if he's Italian?
我想知道他是不是意大利人？
- Ah, grazie, mamma.
- 啊，谢谢妈妈。
Mmm.
嗯。
- I bet Dawn's the odd quad.
- 我打赌Dawn是那个与众不同的。
She's a girl.
她是个女孩。
We're all boys.
我们都是男孩。
It's obviously her.
显然是她。
- Girls rule.
- 女孩最棒。
- I bet Ricky's the odd quad.
- 我打赌Ricky是那个与众不同的。
He thinks he's so much smarter than us.
他认为他比我们聪明得多。
- No, thank you, mother.
- 不，谢谢妈妈。
I already know everything.
我已经知道所有事情了。
- I bet Dicky's the odd quad.
- 我打赌Dicky是那个奇怪的四轮车。
He eats shoe bologna.
他吃鞋形波洛尼亚香肠。
- Sweet feet meat.
- 甜美的脚肉。
- Come on, guys. - Yeah, hats and beards.
- 来吧，伙计们。 - 是的，帽子和胡子。
Let's go. - Ah, there you go.
我们走吧。 - 啊，就这样。
- Awesome. - All right, quads.
- 太棒了。 - 好了，四轮车们。
Looking good.
看起来不错。
And...
然后...
action!
开始！
- Four tires and seven years ago...
- 四轮胎和七年前...
- Our father bought a set of all-weather radials
- 我们的父亲从Honest Abe's购买了一套全季节轮胎
from Honest Abe's.
- 在那里，你保证能得到
- Where you're guaranteed to get
- 四只完美匹配的轮胎
four perfectly matching tires
- 它们能完美和谐地工作，
that work in perfect harmony,
- 就像四轮摩托车一样。
just like quads.
- 就像我们这样的四轮摩托车。
- Quads like us.
- 呃，但有时候
- Uh, but sometimes
- 三只匹配的轮胎和一只完全不相关的轮胎
three matching tires and one completely unrelated tire
- 也挺好的。
are good too.
也不错。
- Cut!
停！
Aw, I miss them Kramden Quads.
哎，我怀念克拉姆登四胞胎。
- Kids, are you okay?
孩子们，你们还好吗？
- We can't do this, Dad.
我们做不到，爸爸。
We're not really family.
我们并不是真正的家人。
- [sighs] Guys, I want you
大家，我想让你们看看这个。
to look at something.
哇，看看我们，
- Wow, look at us,
回到我们以为我们是一家人那时候。
back when we thought we were all family.
好吧，你们认为家人是什么？
- Okay, what do you think family is?
- 那么，你认为家庭是什么？
- People who are actually related?
- 实际上有血缘关系的人？
- Is that all?
- 就这些吗？
Look at those pictures. - Hmm.
看看那些照片。 - 嗯。
- Do you see any DNA up there?
- 你看到上面的DNA了吗？
- I don't.
- 我没有。
All I see are is four kids
我只看到四个孩子
who came into this world together,
他们一起来到这个世界，
who grew up together,
一起长大，
who argue about everything together,
一起争论所有事情，
but at the end of the day,
但到了一天结束时，
they come back together and they love each other.
他们会重新聚在一起，彼此相爱。
- Now, if that's not family, I don't know what is.
- 如果这还不算家人，那我不知道什么才算了。
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，各位。
I just got a text from my Mom.
我刚收到我妈的短信。
She retested the DNA samples,
她重新检测了DNA样本，
and we found out which one of you isn't related.
我们发现你们中有一个不是亲生的。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
It doesn't matter anymore.
这已经不重要了。
- We don't want to know.
- 我们不想知道。
- Because no matter what that stupid DNA test says...
因为无论那个愚蠢的DNA测试说什么...
we are family.
我们都是一家人。
- Absolutely.
绝对没错。
But just out of curiosity.
但出于好奇。
- It's the one who's part terrier.
是那个有部分是㹴犬的人。
- Wait, what? - Huh?
等等，什么？
- One of us is a dog?
我们中有一个是狗？
- Well, I guess that explains
嗯，我想这解释了
my adorable puppy-dog eyes.
我那可爱的狗狗眼。
- No, Dicky, you're not part dog.
不，迪基，你不是狗的一部分。
One of the samples must have been contaminated.
其中一个样本肯定被污染了。
- By Squishy!
- 是Squishy！
- He's been chewing on everything lately.
- 他最近一直在啃咬所有东西。
- [barking]
- [吠叫]
- See, you are all related, just like we said.
- 看，你们都是相关的，就像我们说的那样。
- This is a real sweet family moment,
- 这真是一个温馨的家庭时刻，
but I got to be honest.
但我得说实话。
You four are out.
你们四个出局了。
I'm going a whole new way.
我要走一条全新的路。
Whoo!
喔！
[patriotic music]
Honest Abe's Tires.
诚实亚伯轮胎。
For when the road gets...
当道路变得...
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ 耶耶，耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪